

+380 97 447 37 66 svyryd2012@gmail.com Kyiv, Ukraine

About me

I'm a Frontend developer with more than 1 year of development experience.

I passed several courses and learned all necessary knowledge related to Frontend development. I have read all official React documentation, and continue to study React on the different resources.

I also have a little experience with Node.js and Express.js.

Skills

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- React, Redux
- Bootstrap, Ant Design
- Git, Github
- RESTful APIs
- SQL, MongoDB
- Figma

Languages

Ukrainian: Native

English: Intermediate

Links

Github

Portfolio

LinkedIn

Work experience

Frontend developer at CNAP, Rivne

May, 2022 — July, 2022 (3 months).

I performed the following tasks:

- Creating a design of the Administrative Services Center website.
- Website development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Transferring the site to the WordPress.
- Adding electronic queue and Newsline using WordPress.

Software engineer at RenomeSmart, Rivne

November, 2021 — June, 2022 (9 months).

I interned and performed the following tasks:

- Designing a parking system.
- Creating a layout of the parking application in Figma.
- User interface testing.
- Presentation of the project to local authorities.

Education

National university of life and environmental sciences of Ukraine, Kyiv

September 2022 — Present.

Bachelor, specialty 121 "Software Engineering".

Rivne professional college of national university of life and environmental sciences of Ukraine, Rivne

September 2018 — June 2022 (4 years).

Junior specialist, specialty 121 "Software Engineering".

Courses/Certificates

Aug 2022 — Aug 2022	JavaScript Advanced, ITVDN

Jul 2022 — Aug 2022 HTML & CSS Essential, ITVDN

Oct 2021 — Nov 2021 IT Essential, Cisco Academy